

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Argentinian - Italian citizenship 27 years

IT Support - Frontend Developer

HOW TO CONTACT ME

+49 01522 5431989

me@marcopianaroli.com

https://marcopianaroli.com

Schreinerstrasse 11, 10247, Berlin

ABOUT ME

I enjoy collaborating in teams, where we can exchange knowledge and experiences to achieve common goals. Simultaneously, my ability to work autonomously and organized allows me to successfully tackle projects and individual tasks, demonstrating adaptability to various work dynamics. With a combination of technical skills and customer orientation I am committed to making a significant and positive contribution in dynamic and challenging professional environments.

LANGUAGES

- Native Spanish
- English C1
- German B1

WORK EXPERIENCE

OKAPI GMBH - BERLIN

Web Master | August 2022- Currently

- Updates and maintenance tasks
- Front End Developing
- Execute SEO techniques to boost organic traffic
- IT Support
- Hardware/software troubleshooting

OKAPI GMBH - BERLIN

Warehouse worker | Jan 2021- August 2022

- Picking and packing
- Inventory management
- Equipment operation and maintenance
- Quality control

COMPAÑIA URBANA - BUENOS AIRES

IT Support | August 2019 - October 2020

- Data entry.
- Hardware troubleshooting.
- First level support.
- Hardware troubleshooting. Components replacement.
- Use of Office, Teams, Outlook and Team Viewer/Any Desk.
- · ServiceDesk Plus ticketing system.

EDUCATION

2019 - Currently - Self Learning

- VueJS
- Clean Code
- Design Patterns
- Project designing/building

2020 - 2021 - IT Support

- End-to-end customer support
- Identifying problems to troubleshooting and debugging
- Utilize common problem-solving methodologies and soft skills in an Information Technology setting.

2017 - 2019 - EducacionIT

- Software Testing
- HTML/CSS/Javascript
- · Responsive Design
- Git / Version Control

2014 - Instituto Cardenal Spinola, Buenos Aires.

- High school degree in economics and administration.
- Annual Cambridge exams with certifications.
- Annual Microsoft Office exams with certifications.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Knoweledge in Vue.js, Nuxt, TypeScript, JavaScript.
- Experienced with Nuxt.js for building scalable applications.
- Skilled in HTML, CSS, and Tailwind CSS for creating responsive and visually appealing interfaces.
- Familiar with Microsoft Office suite for effective documentation and communication.

TEDXSANISIDRO: IDEAS WORTH SPREADING

Volunteer in the organization of the events | 2015 - 2019

- · Customer service.
- Speaker's support.
- Assembly and disassembly of the infrastructure before and after the events.

CENCOSUD - BUENOS AIRES

Administrative | October 2016 - October 2018.

- Help desk.
- Training new employees.
- Data entry.

PROFESSIONAL INFORMATION

I have a solid background in IT support, self-learning, and volunteer work, giving me a diverse skill set. Starting in Argentina and expanding to Berlin, I've provided end-to-end customer support, troubleshooting, and debugging. My work ethics and skills gave me the oportunity to transition to a Webmaster role responsibilities, front-end development, and IT support. Throughout my journey, I've demonstrated a commitment to growth, continually enhancing both my technical expertise and interpersonal skills.

SKILLS

- Active directory management
- Operating system management:
 Windows, Linux and Mac
- Ease on building PCs
- Oral and written communication
- Teamwork
- Time management